Gabriel Lombardi

+55 51 99958 3315

gabriellomba@gmail.com

inlinkedin.com/in/gabriel-lombardi-9aaa16154/

Summary

Data science and big data analytics student, and graduate in engineering by the Federal University of Rio Grande do Sul, focusing on production and process engineering. With experience in project development, is focusing currently in optimization and automation of processes and functions through programming languages.

Experience

Planning and control consultant – March 2020 to December 2022 **MRV engineering**, Porto Alegre and Florianópolis.

- Costs management and service planning to improve strategy and process mapping.
- Developing projects to ensure the process flow.
- Ensuring conformity in building plans.
- Cooperating in effective, safe and sustainable construction sites.
- Process mapping.

Safety engineering intern – February 2020 to March 2020 **NR Medical and Engineering**, Curitiba

- Workplace safety consulting.
- Elaboration of workplace risk management plans.

Civil engineering intern – March 2017 to December 2017 **Alves, Fardin Engineering**, Porto Alegre

- Infrastructure Project analysis.
- Budgeting.
- Overseeing construction sites.

Engineering intern – January 2017 to March 2017

Hotel Consulte, Porto Alegre

- Hotel implantation.
- Logistics and quality.
- Budgeting, hiring and supervising activities.
- Team management.

Education

Data Science and big data analysis – currently studying **Universidade Estácio de Sá (UNESA)**.

Bachelor of Engineering: Civil Engineering - 2019 Federal University of Rio Grande do Sul (UFRGS), RS

Post-graduation: Safety engineering – incomplete

Federal University of Technology - PR

Additional activities

- Software experience: Excel, Visual Basic, Power BI, Word, PowerPoint, Project, Revit, AutoCAD 2D
 & 3D, Sony Vegas, SAP ECC;
- Programming Certifications: Python, Django, MySQL, Power BI Udemy 2023;
- Certifications: Six-sigma Yellow belt certification 2015, Open dojo program, development of human competencies, strategic and entrepreneurship skills - Universidade da Experiência Uexp – Curitiba - 2016;
- Volunteering activities: **Construction working in emergency houses** Teto Paraná 2016;
- Internacional experience: CISV camps from 2010 through 2013 and AFS exchange program in Italy 2012:
- Scientific initiation: Institute of hydraulic research UFRGS 2015. Technological Innovation Fair FINOVA UFRGS 2015.
- Published Articles: ANALYSIS OF THE DISCHARGE COEFFICIENT BEHAVIOR IN SMALL CONDUIT
 SYSTEMS AN EXPERIMENTAL STUDY XXI Brazilian symposium of water resources. Energy and water efficiency in sanitation Academic journal: Revista da Extensão UFRGS PROREXT.

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Problem solving
- Organization
- Planning and control
- Process mapping
- Cooperation

Languages

- Portuguese fluent
- English fluent
- Italian advanced
- Japanese beginner